Hello friends, experience is such a thing that
comes to you after you have lost all your hair and something similar happens with us
in the stock market also, by the time we
get that experience, all our
capital is lost Hello friends, welcome to
our channel DSPT
where we have brought for you many
technically sound and strong stocks and
after continuously giving you many such picks back to back, we have once again come in front of you with another
pick named
ICICI Prudential Life Insurance, we will
look at it along with charts and fundamental
research and used and we will tell you where to take entry and where to exit in this stock,
you will be with us
till the end of this video and before that, we have a small
request to the new viewers, please
subscribe to the channel and like it
and click on the bell icon
because whenever you get a notification,
you will be able to see our new pick in time
Hello friends, before coming to the chart of the talk, let
us first know some fundamentals of the
52-week of the stock  High 530 7.30
52-week low was 26.10 and if we talk about one year return
then it gave a return of
17.67 percent this company has a market capital of
349 4 crores if we talk about turnover then it has had a
turnover of Twenty20 since 2019
friends as you can see on the screen
600 800 in 0685020 if we talk about net profit then there is a
slight black in net profit
1014 3.65 crores till 2006
2.75 crores this is only a slight difference it is
not that big if you
talk about tally results then the company has
posted a net profit of 26.86 crores in the June quarter which is more than the March
2 end last year same quarter June
quarter and as you
know that due to best friend mix
people have become very worried about their life
and believe this  The
MD of this company is N.S. Khanan ji and he
says that as
fear has now arisen in the minds of people regarding life, their interest in
life products is also increasing and he
expects that
they can have more turnover and profit in the coming quarters.
Friends,
in the technical point of this Totka channel, we are going to discuss many
charts and will
develop conferences on Street. So let
us quickly see this monthly chart.
Friends, you can see that
in Rally stock, the ministerial support is of 374 and the
ministerial resistance is of 1428.
This stock is also straight at 450 carats
and 420 has been a safety issue for you for a
long time. So, you should keep this one layer in mind till the
end of the video. This level is
very important. In the next test,
friends, the second chart, friends, we have
taken the weekly time series where you will
see three levels. 428 is common, 400 has
increased by one, 374 is where 428 is. If
I were to tell you after looking at this chart, then 428
You should wait for it to come. See
what happens. We get
angry after seeing bullish news or some trend
in the stock and it becomes very
difficult to get out of there because the stock from there.
But sometimes you must have also thought that when
you buy this stock, it starts
coming down right away. Why? Because after
seeing the news or that friend has got caught, you will
not be able to
catch it. Thinking like this, you
take the train and start tracking and
after that there is resistance, from there the
stop starts falling and you go to the last and keep
averaging at every level,
after that you are not able to get out.
Like this is a very good example of this
thing.
So let's move to the next chart, friends. This
Bollinger Band, which we use in every one of our
videos, is a very powerful
indicator, a powerful tool. You
see, if you do Reserve Bank with a great,
then think about this mode, this attraction, this attraction is
bringing you here. Now look here, along with this
Bollinger Band, on the screen line
also, you will see twice around 10 line
giving you support again.  It has already
touched the upper band of the Reserve Bank of India,
and generally it is said that
when a stock touches this level, then
Musharraf is found, but here I am waiting a little bit for the
bears of this level, if it reaches
here then it should definitely
reach 428 and the
metal band of Bollinger Bands also says that once the
stock reaches this level, then
this is the Bollinger Band.
Moving on to the next chart, friends, to increase
your confidence, I have
added a trend line here on the daily chart itself.
See, this stock has
taken support on this trend line,
yes, for the second time in the third time,
it has moved upwards from here, so now you can
see the trend on one and a half charts, in these technical matters are totally different from the history, so history repeats itself, so you see, I will give
you a touch here, see, if you
respect the friendliner trend, then
friends, just to increase your confidence on the daily chart,
I have
shown you this first.  All this is the chart, these lines are
our stagnant, they are not from here, they have the same
labels, I am showing you the same, you can do next,
friends, this is
Supertrend with this strategy,
we have not inputted our techniques in this, let me
tell you a little about Supertrend, whenever Supertrend
is above the price section, then this
track remains balanced, when it comes below the price candles,
Supertrend gives you a
bullish signal,
for a confirmation, I have put this message here
that this is fast follow, this is fast
and this reduce slogan and here it
cut it and after that our Supertrend came
down to the price, so
you have seen a bulletproof, from here it is continuously
and is continuously trading above this, thank you, it had
rebelled here, but
still it did not come below Supertrend, it has
taken support and has started its journey again, so
a new one, we
showed you the technical tour
about Supertrend, if you want to know friends and
what is Supertrend, then
you  Write to us in the comment box,
we will make another video about it and
share it with you.
Let's move on to another new chart where I have
used three technical tips and which
always gives you a double tax. Friends, this is
my tree indicator study. Topic stock.
Here we get only arrears. This is the lower
part and this is Mercedes and here these
candles are visible but the line
visible below it is dust printed in this which can be
called a very powerful use flower.
You see, the remedy has filled
you with positive eyes. Here above Rs. 60 there
is bangles and glass and
above the appointed SK, this is already great. The
stock is doing from here till here, you
can see, so I think friends,
after teaching you so many charts,
I have developed it in a lot of conferences and you
can take bread in it, defined our
labels, you listen, again there is 428 brother,
after that there is 410 and after that 374
is far behind, but as long as you have been in it,
when  Till then it remains above the front and
in the near term I will not tell you this target like this
because first I will
make a video and send it to you that I am going to give you a target of 358 percent,
you will get it easily in this, there will be no
problem and for now this is all
we have for this stock
and we will meet next with another video,
another technical university is
reaching there and only then
stay safe from Corona and like this video,
subscribe to new people and share
our channel with your friends and
expand the Tasty family